Get it at the smallest one you can.
There you go, nice job, nice clean job.
And, you really, really want to use wire strippers, because it just gets a little too frustrating if you don't have this.
Because it gets a little bit hard to strip the wire.
There you have it.
And all your wire's stripped.
Just about an inch on each side, because don't forget, that the rubber that's around this wire insulates this.
So, you have to have this open to charge, and this is why you go ahead and strip the ends of it.
But you don't want to strip it here, because you want to keep it insulated.
But you can still let the flow of electrons go through, so you can make your telegraph.